{
    "subject": "resource/Anti-Scrunti_Faction",
    "predicate": "property/origin",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "The Anti-Scrunti Faction originated from the United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9363899230957031,
            "question": "Where did the Anti-Scrunti Faction originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8249344229698181,
            "question": "When did the Anti-Scrunti Faction emerge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7915093302726746,
            "question": "Are there any known historical figures associated with the Anti-Scrunti Faction?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6650106310844421,
            "question": "What country is associated with the Anti-Scrunti Faction?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5952370762825012,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the Anti-Scrunti Faction?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49875006079673767,
            "question": "What were the main beliefs or goals of the Anti-Scrunti Faction?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48954612016677856,
            "question": "What were some of the challenges faced by the Anti-Scrunti Faction?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4832996726036072,
            "question": "Did the Anti-Scrunti Faction have any significant influence on events?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47889673709869385,
            "question": "How did the Anti-Scrunti Faction interact with other groups or movements of their time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4182688593864441,
            "question": "Is there any information available about the lasting impact of the Anti-Scrunti Faction?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Anti-Scrunti Faction originated from the United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_809_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did the Anti-Scrunti Faction interact with other groups or movements of their time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_809_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did the Anti-Scrunti Faction have any significant influence on events?",
            "html": "dbpedia_809_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were some of the challenges faced by the Anti-Scrunti Faction?",
            "html": "dbpedia_809_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_809_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_809_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_809_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_809_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_809_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_809_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_809_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_809_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_809_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_809_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided supports that \u201cAnti Scrunti Faction\u201d (A.S.F.) originated from Boulder, Colorado, which is in the United States. Therefore, the statement that The Anti-Scrunti Faction originated from the United States is correct based on the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}